jkdress-shop.com 2014-03-06

# Privacy Policy | JKDress Shop

JKDress-Shop.com respects your privacy and secures your online safety seriously. In order to provide you with the best products, efficient customer service, we record a variety of information from your visit to our site. To better protect your privacy, we would like to explain our online information practices and the way your information is collected and used.

We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read our Privacy Notice. By visiting our Site, you accept the practices described in this Notice. This privacy policy does not necessarily apply to our offline collection of your personal information. Please see below for details. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any non-JKDress-Shop.com website to which this Site links to or that links to our site.  
I) Information Collection

We collect information from you in several different ways on this Site. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. We can use your personal information to:

\- Help make this Web-Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information once again.  
\- Help you quickly find information, products, and services.  
\- Alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer.  
(a) Registration and Ordering. Before using certain parts of this Site or ordering products, you must complete online registration. During registration, you will be prompted to provide us with certain personal information, including your name, living address, shipping address(es), phone number, email address, and credit card number. These kinds of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and our site, and for internal marketing purposes.  
(b) Email Addresses. If you agree your email address can be use for: Free promotional notices; to answer your request to inform you with a new brand, or new product style; to  
sign up for our email newsletter.  
(c) Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. We have to use cookies to enable you to select products, place them in an online shopping cart, and to purchase those products. If you do this, we keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase. Our cookies are not “spyware.”  
(d) Log Files. As is true of most websites, the Site server automatically recognizes the Internet URL from which you access this Site. We may also log your Internet protocol (“IP”) address, Internet service provider, and date/time stamp for system administration, order verification, internal marketing, and system troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address may indicate the location of your computer on the Internet.)  
(e) Age. We respect children’s privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. Elsewhere on this Site, you have represented and warranted that you are either 18 years of age or using the Site with the supervision of a parent or guardian. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you.

II) Information Use and Disclosure

(a) Internal Use. We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve our Site’s content and layout, to improve our outreach and for our own marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you), and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to this Site.  
(b) Communications with You. We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our site, and your orders and deliveries. Also, we may send you a confirmation email when you register with us. Because we have to communicate with you about orders that you choose to place, you cannot opt out of receiving emails related to your orders.  
(c) External Use. We want to provide you with excellent service and to offer you a great selection — we primarily sell merchandise, not information. We do not sell, rent, trade, license, or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone, except: third parties such as post office, Fedex, DHL to ship products.

III) DATA SECURITY

We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online, and we also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information.

Upon your request, we will (a) correct or update your personal information; (b) stop sending emails to your email address; and/or (c) disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account. You can make these requests at the customer information section, or by telephoning, or emailing your request to JKDress Customer Support department at service@jkdress-shop.com. Please do not email your credit card number or other sensitive information.

IV) UPDATES TO THIS POLICY

If we change or update this Privacy Notice, we will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Notice from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Notice has been changed or updated.

If you have any questions about the Privacy Notice, please contact us at info@jkdress-shop.com.
